Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series II: Committees and Boards, 1976-2015; 40.78 Linear Feet in 92 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  - Flier Distribution (Deans), 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Housing Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 9-10)
  - Media Task Force, 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1998-1999 (Box 207, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1998-1999 (Box 207, Folder 3-6)
  - Student Center Planning Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Student Councils, 1998-1999 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Student Health Subcommittee, 1998-1999 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Student Services (Food, Health), 1998-1999 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 208, Folder 6-7)
  - Academic Affairs, 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Academic Support Services, 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1999-2000, 2007-2011 (Box 209, Folder 2, Box 250, Folder 3-4)
  - Coles Advisory, 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Computers (NYU Net, Internet), Working Group on Tech, 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Judicial Board, 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Kimmel Center Transition Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Media Task Force, 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1999-2000 (Box 210, Folder 8-9)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1999-2000 (Box 211, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Councils, 1999-2000 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Student Health Subcommittee, 1999-2000 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Student Services (Food, Health) Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 1999-2000 (Box 211, Folder 7, Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Coles Advisory Board/Recreation, 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Communications Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Committee Chairs, 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 1-3)
  - Faculty Relations Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Financial Aid Office Advisory Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Judicial Board, 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 4-6)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 7, Box 215, Folder 1-4)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Student Grievance Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Student Services Committee (Food, Health), 2000-2001 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 216, Folder 1-2)
  - Senate Select Committee, 2001 (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2001-2002 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 216, Folder 5-6)
  - Financial Affairs, 2001-2002 (Box 250, Folder 8)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 2001-2002 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Grievance Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2001-2002 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2001-2002 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Judicial Board, 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Kimmel Center Advisory Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Media Task Force, 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 5-6)
  - Student Councils, 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2001-2002 (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 218, Folder 1-4)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Academic Support Services Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee on Undergraduate Affairs, 2002-2003 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2002-2003 (Box 219, Folder 3-4)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 2002-2003 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Community Service Council, 2002-2003 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 220, Folder 1-4)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 2002-2003 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Grievance Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Housing Committee Background, 1995-1998, 2002-2003 (Box 251, Folder 2-4)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Judicial Board, 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Media Task Force, 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Senate Financial Affairs Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2002-2003 (Box 221, Folder 8-9)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2002-2003 (Box 222, Folder 1-4)
  - Student Councils, 2002-2003 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Student/Faculty Relations Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2002-2003 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 2002-2003 (Box 223, Folder 4-5)
  - WTSA Prog NY Students, 2002-2003 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0014)
    Tape was in folder labeled "SSC/UCSL - Executive Committee"
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Committee for Engagement and Diversity, 2003-2004 (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2003-2004 (Box 223, Folder 7-8)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 224, Folder 1-3, Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 2003-2004 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Community Service Council, 2003-2004 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Diversity Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 224, Folder 7-8, Box 225, Folder 1-2)
  - Financial Affairs, 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 3, Box 251, Folder 8)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Grievance Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Judicial Board, 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 9)
  - Kimmel Center Advisory Board, 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 10)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 225, Folder 11)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2003-2004 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2003-2004 (Box 226, Folder 2-5, Box 251, Folder 9)
  - Student Councils, 2003-2004 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2003-2004 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 2003-2004 (Box 227, Folder 3-4)
  - Academic Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2004-2005 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Relations, 2004-2005 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Class Councils (SSC), 2004-2005 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 2004-2005 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 228, Folder 3-5)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2004-2005 (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Judicial Board, 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB) - General Information, 2004-2005, 2011-2012 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Student Councils, 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Student Services, 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 229, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Academic Support Services Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Class Councils (SSC), 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 7-8)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 9)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 2005-2006 (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 231, Folder 1-2)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2005-2006 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2005-2006 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - School Student Councils, 2005-2006 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2005-2006 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2005-2006 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2005-2006 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 2005-2006 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senators Council Annual Dinner, 2006 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2006-2007 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 232, Folder 10)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2006-2007 (Box 232, Folder 11)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2006-2007 (Box 232, Folder 12)
  - New Club Development (NCD) Evaluations, 2006-2007 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2006-2007 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2006-2007 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2006-2007 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Student Services Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - School Student Councils, 2006-2007 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 2006-2007 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Academic Support Service Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2007-2010 (Box 233, Folder 10-11)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 1-2)
  - Faculty Council, 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 4-5)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Judicial Board, 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - New Club Development (NCD) Evaluations, 2007-2008 (Box 234, Folder 10, Box 235, Folder 1-2)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2007-2008 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2007-2008 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Student Councils in Schools, 2007-2008 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2007-2008 (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 2007-2008 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box 235, Folder 9)
  - Academic Support Services Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - All Square Budget Advisory Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 2008-2009 (Box 236, Folder 2-3)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) - Reallocations, 2008-2009 (Box 236, Folder 4-5)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) & Student Activities Board (SAB) Merger, 2008-2009 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Relation Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - Class (Councils) Activities Board, 2008-2009 (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - Committee Chairs, 2008-2009 (Box 236, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 1-2)
  - Faculty Senators Council, 2008-2012 (Box 237, Folder 3-4)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Grievance Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 10)
  - Judicial Board, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 11)
  - List of Clubs, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 12)
  - New Club Development (NCD) - General, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 13)
  - New Club Development (NCD) - Not Completed, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 14)
  - Off-Campus Student Councils (OCSC), 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 15)
  - Office of Student Activities (OSA) New Club Development Program - Progress Report & Final Evaluation, 2008-2009 (Box 237, Folder 16, Box 238, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Student Health Advisory Board, 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Student Services, 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - School Student Councils, 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - South Asian Student Association (SHRUTI), 2009 (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - All Square Club Budget Workshop - Returning Clubs Apply for 2009-2010 ASSABC Funding (Box 238, Folder 10)
  - All Square Student Budget Allocation Committee - Reallocations, 2009, 2011 (Box 238, Folder 11)
  - Senate Financial Affairs Committee (SFAC), 2010-2011 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 2009-2012 (Box 239, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB)/All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Financial Affairs International Affairs, 2010-2011 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB)- Correspondence/Appeals, 2011 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB)- New Club Development (NCD) Final Evaluations, 2009-2010 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 2012 (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - Student Activities Board, 2013 (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - Student Technology and Research Committee, 2014 (Box 239, Folder 9)
  - New Club Development (NCD) Application, 2014-2015 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Superblock Stewardship Advisory Committee (SSAC), 2014-2015 (Box 240, Folder 2-3)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB) - New Club in Development Petitions, 2014-2015 (Box 240, Folder 4-6, Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 2015 (Box 241, Folder 2-3)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 2015 (Box 241, Folder 4)
- Series III: Agendas & Minutes, 1975-2016; 13.48 Linear Feet in 29 manuscript boxes and 1 shared cassette box
  Series III contains agendas and minutes related to the Student Senators Council's monthly meetings. The SSC meets every month and discusses a range of topics relevant to student life at NYU. The agendas contain information such as roll call, approval of minutes, announcements, reports from the chairman, and committee reports. Topics discussed in the meeting minutes include committee reports, organization and governance, finances, new business, election information, and judicial board information.
  - Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Student Senator Caucus, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Student Senators Council, 1977 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0011)
  - Agendas & Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Senators Council - Agenda & Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - University Committee on Student Life - Agendas & Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
  - Untitled Audiocassette Tape, 1978-1979 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0010)
    Tape is not labeled, but was found in a folder labeled "SSC - Agenda and Minutes."
  - Senate, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC), 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Agendas & Minutes (USCL), 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
  - Handicapped Students, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Housing, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Parliamentarian, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Publicity, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Smoking, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Standardized Testing, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - University Investments, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC), 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL), 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 13-14, Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Discrimination: Placement Office, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Meeting with the President, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Resident Fellow Program, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Senate Strategy, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Smoking Section, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Special Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0012)
  - Stipends for Teaching Assistants, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - School of the Arts (SOA) Student Council Secretary, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - United Staff Association, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL), 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - Higher Education Program: School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP), 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 14, Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Judicial Board, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Student Senators Council - Agenda & Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
  - Agendas & Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 5-6, Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Chairman's Remarks, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Open House: Office of Career, etc…, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square News, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Summer Meetings: Memos & Agendas, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Union Strike, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Agendas & Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
  - Minutes & Memorandum, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 9, Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Academic Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 3-5)
  - AIDS, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Announcements, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Attendance at Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Academic Year 1986-1987, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Chairperson's Report, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Commencement, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Councils and Constituencies, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Election of Officers, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committees, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Financial Affairs (Senate), 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Health Services, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Housing, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Information Center, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Integrity of Scientific Research, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Judicial Board, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - NYU Security Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - President's, Chancellor's Remarks, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Rules & Organization, SSC Ad Hoc Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Rules of Procedure, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Student Information System (SIS), 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Tuition Assistance Program (TAP), 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs (AIDS), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 11-12)
  - Attendance at Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Bureaucracy Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Chairman's Reports & Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Committee Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Coors Beer, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Earth Valley, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Council Membership Information, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Government Relations, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Affairs, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Hands Around the Park, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Health Week & AIDS, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Housing, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Kudos, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Meetings with Vice President Marcus, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Minutes & Agendas (UCSL), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous Student Activities, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Missing Children, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - NYU Student Lobby (NYUSLA), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 5)